Ò×¿¼·¶ÎÄÊ®
What an inspiring picture!
A cluster of people are playing rope-skipping together, keeping in step.
Two men swaying the rope on each side are counting.
On careful observation,
we may discover that one of them counts to ninety-nine,
while the other one hundred.
It seems to me that the painter intends to point out that
the construction of a harmonious society demands our joint effort and that
there may be phenomena that disrupt our social harmony.
Although it is by no means a simple task to build a society
in which people live in harmony with each other and with the nature,
we are confident that if everyone contributes to the cause,
many hands will make light work.
At the same time, it would be unlikely to realize our long-term development goals
unless we remain conscious of some widespread problems.
There is no denying that we are confronted with
increasingly acute social unrest resulting from growing disparity
between developed coastal area and underdeveloped west,
widening gap of the wealthy and the poor,
environment pollution and government corruption.
Since a disharmonious society is not liable to survive hard times,
it is of great significance that we make concerted effort to eliminate problems
and establish a harmonious and prosperous society.